<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <XenotypeDef>
    <defName>VREH_Uhlan</defName>
    <label>uhlan</label>
    <description>Uhlans are a side-development from captured hussars, turned by certain elements to become a counter to the military-developed supersoldier programs. Their genetic dependence on luciferium is both a deterrent against capturing and an improvement to long-term usefulness.\n\nAppropriately named demons for their permanently flushed skin and intense bloodthirst, uhlans are incredibly resilient and specialized in certain styles of combat. Quite often they are decked out in heavy armor, in which they can charge full tilt at their intended target.\n\nExtremely specialized and on a permanent hair-trigger, there has been much speculation that their development was sponsored by megacorporations as part of the latest arms race. No substantial evidence has been presented to support these claims.</description>
    <descriptionShort>Uhlans are engineered super-soldiers who fight aggressively and without emotion. They heal extremely fast, glide through obstacles using their small wings, freely ingest military drugs and rely on luciferium to keep their bodies functioning.</descriptionShort>
    <iconPath>UI/XenotypeIcons/Uhlan</iconPath>
    <combatPowerFactor>1.5</combatPowerFactor>
    <genes>
      <li>Hair_ShortOnly</li>
      <li>Body_Standard</li>
      <li>Eyes_Red</li>
      <li>Body_Hulk</li>
	  <li>Skin_DeepRed</li>
	  <li>Skin_PaleRed</li>
      <li>WoundHealing_SuperFast</li>
      <li>Pain_Reduced</li>
      <li>Unstoppable</li>
      <li>MaxTemp_SmallIncrease</li>
      <li>MinTemp_SmallDecrease</li>
      <li>AptitudeRemarkable_Shooting</li>
      <li>AptitudeRemarkable_Melee</li>
      <li>ToxicEnvironmentResistance_Partial</li>
      <li>Aggression_HyperAggressive</li>
      <li>AptitudeTerrible_Plants</li>
      <li>AptitudeTerrible_Animals</li>
      <li>AptitudeTerrible_Social</li>
      <li>AptitudeTerrible_Artistic</li>
      <li>AddictionImmune_GoJuice</li>
	  <li>KillThirst</li>
      <li>VREH_ChemicalDependency_Luciferium</li>
	  <li>VREH_Toughness</li>
	  <li>VREH_Glidewings</li>
	  <li>VREH_BulletproofSkin</li>
	  <li>VREH_Giant</li>
	  <li>VREH_Arrogant</li>
	  <li>VREH_Unconstrained</li>
	  <li>VREHT_WeaponAptitude_Randomizer</li>
    </genes>
  </XenotypeDef>

</Defs>